Hi!
I'm Robin with trees-mom.com.
We're crocheting wire to make a Christmas bracelet.
On your crochet hook, if you've never crocheted before, you need to remember to hold the crochet hook parallel to your body, horizontal to the floor.
The hook part is always towards you.
Your thumb will go on the little part that's indented and your fingers just wrap around the crochet hook.
You just hold it just like this.
Sort of like you might hold a spoon or a fork.
This is the way I do it.
It might not be the proper way to hold a crochet hook, but it works well for crocheting wire, which is a lot different than crocheting yarn.
Just always remember to keep the hook part towards you and to keep the crochet hook horizontal with the floor, and you shouldn't have any problems with holding your crochet hook.